Otto Sternoff Beyer Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Speech and Article File, 1919-1947 (Box 115-124)
  - Texts (Box 116)
    - 1935 Nov., "How Development of Personnel Has Contributed to Progress of the Transportation Industry"
    - 1937
      - Mar., "Collective Bargaining Under the Railway Labor Act"
      - June, "What Engineers Should Know about Labor Problems"
    - 1938
      - Feb., "Railroad Labor Relations Today
      - Mar., "Collective Bargaining and Labor Management Cooperation"
      - May, "A Practical Program for the Coordination of Government, Labor and Management"
      - June, Winant Speech, Geneva, Switzerland
      - Oct., "The Art of Mediation"
      - Dec., "Mediation"
    - 1939
      - May, "Making Democracy Work"
      - June, "Making Collective Bargaining Work"
      - Dec., Convention
    - 1940 (Box 118)
      - Jan.
        - Round Table Discussion, National Conference of Christians and Jews
        - "Engineers as Arbitrators"
      - Mar., "Mediation, the Next Step"
      - July, Address before Convention of Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees
      - Oct., "Total Cooperation"
      - Nov., "Labor's Contribution to Industry"
      - Dec., "Government's Role in Collective Bargaining"
    - 1941
      - Jan.
        - "Research and Collective Bargaining"
        - "Railway Labor Relations and the National Defense"
      - Mar., "Defense and the National Mediation Board"
    - 1942
      - May, "Manpower, A Pressing Problem"
      - July, "Railroad Manpower Problems in Wartime"
      - July, "Manpower for Railroad Maintenance of Way"
      - Aug., "Mediation and Conciliation"
      - Sept., "Manpower Problems in Mass Transportation"
      - Sept., "Maintenance of Way Manpower Problems," Roadmasters and Maintenance of Way
      - Sept., "Meeting the Manpower Problem"
      - Oct., "Manpower Program for Trucking Industry" (Box 119)
      - Nov., "Human Engineering in Industry"
      - Dec.
        - "The Manpower Problem"
        - "Labor Utilization in Manpower Conservation Program"
    - 1943
      - Jan., "Manpower Problems of the Private Truck Carrier"
      - Mar., "Transportation Workers in Wartime"
      - May, "Railroad Manpower in Wartime"
      - July, "Manpower for the Railroad Maintenance of Way"
      - Oct., "Labor Relations in Wartime"
      - Oct., "Transportation Labor Problems in Wartime and After"
    - 1944
      - Jan., "Railroaders in Wartime"
      - Aug., "Review of Governmental Adjustment of Labor Disputes "
    - 1945
      - "Employee Relations in the Public Service, Present and Future"
    - 1946
      - Jan., "Employee Relations"
      - Aug., "Personnel Management in Industry"
      - Sept., "Fundamentals of Labor-Management Cooperation"
      - Oct., "Bonneville Power and Labor"
    - 1947
      - Jan.
        - "Labor Relations and the Public Service"
        - "Labor Situation," League of Women Voters
      - June, "Employee Relations in Publicly Owned Utilities"
    - Undated
      - American Railroads Under Federal Control
      - "Brotherhood [of Railway Carmen] and Union-Management Cooperation"
      - "Cooperative Research and the Railway Fuel Program"
      - "Democratic Organization of Labor for Cooperative Production"
      - "Industrial Function of the Organized Labor Movement"
      - "Management of Cooperative Factories"
      - "Plan for Establishing Industry Labor Codes"
      - "Productivity of Railway Shop Employees"
    - Draft history regarding railroads (Box 120)
    - Draft history regarding railroads (Box 121)
    - Draft history regarding railroads (Box 122)
    - Draft history regarding railroads (Box 123)
    - Draft history regarding railroads (Box 124)
- Scrapbooks, 1909-1943 (Box 125)
  Bound volumes of printed matter and miscellaneous material.
  Arranged chronologically by volume.
  - 1909 (Box 125)
  - 1923-1930 See Oversize
  - 1926-1936 See Oversize
  - 1933-1934
  - 1938-1939
  - 1942-1943 See Oversize
- Addition, 1933-1951 (Box 126-129)
  Correspondence, reports, notes, articles, memorabilia, and miscellaneous material.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic or type of material.
  - Biographical (Box 126)
    - Printed biographies
    - Bibliography
    - Correspondence
      - Very important
      - General
    - Letters of condolence
    - Appointments to government positions See also Oversize
    - Obituaries
  - Article file
    - History of railroad personnel
    - Labor-management speeches
    - Labor-management study
    - Railroad articles
    - United Textile Workers
    - Utilities
  - Subject file (Box 127)
    - Adjustment boards
    - Alaskan railroads
    - Anglo-American Joint Council
    - Canadian railroads
    - Cost-of-living (newspaper clippings)
    - Eight-hour day
    - Emergency Transport Act of 1933
    - European railroads
    - National Mediation Board
    - Railroad associations
    - Railroad Pension Bill, 1934
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 128)
    - Thirty-hour week
    - Transport personnel
  - Clara Beyer miscellany (Box 129)
    - Correspondence
      - Business, 1938-1951
      - Personal, 1942-1945
      - Social
        - Perkins, Frances
        - White House
    - Memorabilia
    - Notebook of labor legislation, 1939-1945
- Oversize, 1923-1943 (Box OV 1-OV 5)
  Certificates and scrapbooks.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - General Railroad File (Box OV 1)
    - Rail Transport Conference, Geneva, Switzerland
      - 1939
        - Certificate (Container 60)
  - Scrapbooks (Container 125) (Box OV 2)
    - 1923-1930
    - 1926-1936 (Box OV 3)
    - 1942-1943 (Box OV 4)
  - Addition (Box OV 5)
    - Biographical
      - Appointments to government positions, 1935-1936 (Container 126)